Inventory of the A. Piatt Andrew papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Oversize materials, 1909-1936 (Box 50-60)
  - Posters, 1919-1942
    - Announcement of concert by Paul Robeson, Gloucester, Massachusetts, 1942 (Folder 50: 30-31)
  - Scrapbooks, 1904-1936
    - 1904-1914 (Folder 51: 1)
    - 1914-1923 (Folder 52: 1)
    - 1921 (Folder 53: 1)
    - 1921-1930 (Folder 53: 2)
    - 1922 (Folder 54: 1)
    - 1922-1923 (Folder 54: 2)
    - 1925-1926 (Folder 55: 1)
    - 1926-1932 (Folder 55: 2)
    - 1928-1929 (Folder 56: 1)
    - 1929-1930 (Folder 56: 2)
    - 1930 (Folder 57: 1)
    - 1930-1931 (Folder 57: 2)
    - 1931-1932 (Folder 58: 1)
    - 1932 (Folder 58: 2)
    - 1932-1934 (Folder 59: 1)
    - 1932-1936 (Folder 59: 2)
    - 1934-1936 (Folder 60: 1)
    - 1936 (Folder 60: 2)